Guide to the Occupy Wall Street Archives Working Group Records TAM.630
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Poster collected on November 9 -- This system has no future for the youth the revolution does! Revcom.us, 2011 (Box 16)
  22" x 29" White foamcore with red and black marker.
- Poster collected on November 9 -- This is just practice, 2011 (Box 10)
  14" x 18" Brown particleboard with black marker.
- Poster collected on November 9 -- Welcome to the United States, Inc, 2011 (Box 15)
  17.5" x 32.5" Brown cardboard with black and white paint.
- Poster collected on November 9 -- #Occupy Life, 2011 (Box 16)
  17.5" x 32.25" Brown cardboard with red paint and black marker.
- Poster collected on November 9 -- The television will not be revolutionized. Let's occupy!!!, 2011
  22.25" x 40.25" Brown cardboard with green paint.
- Poster collected on November 12 -- Save free markets from the Oligarchs and Kleptocrats, 2011 (Box 8)
  20" x 30" Green foamcore with black marker.
- Poster collected on November 12 -- Image of man reading sign, which reads "Occupy Occupy Occupy...", 2011 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  16.75" x 21.5" Paper with black ink.
- Poster collected on November 12 -- Bankers and toffs get stuffed!, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  20" x 25" Green paper with black ink.
- Poster collected on November 12 -- Image of man eating pie filled with money, titled "American Pie", 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  18" x 23.75" White paper with multi-colored ink. Artist: Michael D'Antuono
- Poster collected on November 12 -- Image of man in suit being comforted by another man, titled "Down & Outsourced", 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  18" x 24" White paper with multi-colored ink. Artist: Michael D'Antuono
- Poster collected on November 12 -- Image of man putting model of United States Capitol building in his pocket, titled "Small Government", 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Poster collected on November 12 -- Ten years ago we've got Steve Jobs, Bob Hope & Johnny Cash. Now, we've got no jobs, no hope, & no cash, 2011
  26" x 34" Brown cardboard with green, blue, and red crayon
- Poster collected on November 14 -- Image of Michael Bloomberg, police officer, and snowstorm over Zuccotti Park, reads "We have to clear that park before the holidays. Turn the H.A.A.R.P. on full blast!! Let's see them occupy the snow.", 2011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  22" x 28" White poster paper with pink, purple, and black marker, with clear tape over paper.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- Image of Barack Obama shining a flashlight into a turkey, reads "Hey ho B.O. Where did all our jobs go? Happy thanksgiving everyone, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  22" x 27.25" White poster paper with black marker.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- Map of United States divided into three sections with numbers in each, reads "Wealth WTF", 2011 (Box 26)
  15.5" x 20.75" White cardboard with black marker.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- Smash the two-party system, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  12" x 18" White poster paper with black marker. Verso reads: We are the 99%
- Poster collected on November 14 -- For the benefit of the whole..., 2011 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  22" x 28" Yellow poster paper with black and red marker.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- Inequality makes my patients sick! PNHP Physicians for a National Health Program New York Metro Chapter, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  22" x 28" White poster paper with black marker, and white paper with green and black ink taped onto poster. Verso reads: "American exceptionalism." Except for: the poor, minorities, students, workers, immigrants, Native-Americans, et al and you!
- Poster collected on November 14 -- I'm a doctor for the 99% PNHP Physicians for a National Health Program New York Metro Chapter, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  22" x 28" White poster paper with black marker, and white paper with green and black ink taped onto poster. Verso reads: Thomas Jefferson said: "When I reflect that God is just, I tremble for my country." America: You will not be absolved of your crimes -against- humanity.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- #OccupierAdvocacy, address greivances, answer questions, navigate bureaucracy. How can we help?, 2011
  23" x 35" Peach poster paper with black marker.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- I'm the 99% fighting for my rights, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  22" x 28" White poster paper with black and red marker.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- We want butter not guns! Listen to us*, 2011 (Box 26)
  12.25" x 24" Brown cardboard with blue marker. Verso reads: Obama lied: No change, transparency, offshore accounts, savings, social security, run away inflation, endless wars
- Poster collected on November 14 -- I want to burn the Turkish flag. Belongs to 1% ruling class, 2011 (Box 8)
  23" x 24" Brown cardboard with black marker.
- Poster -- Organizing through a Racial Justice Framework, #OWS People's Free Library, 2011; cuid34915 (Box 5)
- Poster -- People of Color Working Group!, 2011; cuid34916 (Box 5)
- Poster -- Wisconsin: Workers, Educators, Students, & Artists, We Thank You!, 2011; cuid34913 (Box 6)
- Poster -- Wall Street May Have Money & Influence BUT... The People Got the Power! LiUNA! Laborers Local 108, 2011; cuid34914 (Box 6)
- Poster -- The NYPD stops and frisks hundreds of thousands of innocent people each year, 2011; cuid34880 (Box 9)
- Poster -- Frack Makes 99% Sick, 1% Rich, 2011; cuid34898 (Box 9)
- Poster -- I am Not a Tourist Attraction, Y'all Join the Occupation, 2011; cuid34899 (Box 9)
- Poster -- Occupy Wall Street $pends $4,000 a week on photocopies but still cannot buy a coffee machine that keeps the protesters warm, happy and ready to protest, 2011; cuid34920 (Box 10)
- Poster -- Restore American Airlines Flight Attendants' Wages, 2011; cuid34921 (Box 10)
- Poster -- Trickle Down Economics = Let Them Eat [Urinal] Cake!, 2011; cuid34922 (Box 10)
- Poster -- Eat the Rich! They're Very Tender Cause They Don't Work!!!, 2011; cuid34893 (Box 12)
- Poster -- Can't Stop, Won't Stop, 2011; cuid34894 (Box 12)
- Poster -- Gay Squat 2011-2012, "Come In and Come Out", cuid34918 (Box 13)
- Poster -- Got a Mortgage? A Lease? A Reliable Shelter?... If Not, Join the Houseless Caucus, 2011; cuid34919 (Box 13)
- Poster -- Bank of America, Foreclosed, 2012-03-15; cuid34900 (Box 14)
- Poster -- Arrest Financial Terrorists!! End the Evil Empire (Troops Home from Europe/Asia), 2011; cuid34905 (Box 15)
- Poster -- No Keystone XL Pipeline, 2011; cuid34906 (Box 16)
- Poster -- Want to Be a Billionaire, Too? Work 139,860,139.86 Hours at Min. Wage *Before Taxes, 2011; cuid34907 (Box 16)
- Poster -- Paul Robeson High School Unite!, 2011; cuid34879 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Poster -- OWS Info, Judge ordered park reopened and belongings returned, 2011; cuid34885 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Poster -- Stop Stop + Frisk Tuesday, Nov 1 @ 4pm Brownsville, Brooklyn, nov1action.org, 2011; cuid34884 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Poster -- OWS!, 2011; cuid34881 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Poster -- The Occupied Office Colletive [sic] Agreements, 2011; cuid34882 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Poster -- Turmoil Over Oil, 2011; cuid34883 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Poster -- Follow the Money... All Roads Lead to Wall Street!, 2011; cuid34924 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Poster -- Fight Back World Wide, Capitalism is the Crisis, Decolonize Globally, the 99% Have No Borders, 2011; cuid34925 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Poster -- The 13% Mayor, 2011; cuid34926 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Poster -- Safer Spaces: Rapists Fuck Off, Get Hurt!, 2011; cuid34891 (Box 20)
- Poster -- Surveillance Van, "Smile!", 2011; cuid34892 (Box 20)
- Poster -- When a piece of crap takes a crap, and that crap throws up, then the throw up takes a crap, that's a 401K, 2011; cuid34908 (Box 21)
- Poster -- Bring Our Troops Home So They Can Join Us, 2011; cuid34909 (Box 21)
- Poster -- We Clean, We are Non-Violent, We are Employed, We are Un-Employed..., 2011; cuid34897 (Box 22)
- Poster -- Healthcare for the 99%, 2011; cuid34923 (Box 23)
- Poster -- Kim, Jinsuk (= 300 Days) 'Let's Fight Together!' Solidarity from 99% of Korea, 2011; cuid34887 (Box 25)
- Poster -- The Harder I Work the More I Fall Behind, 2011; cuid34895 (Box 26)
- Poster -- Unite the World, Democracy for All Not Just the 1%, Get Money Out of Politics!, 2011; cuid34896 (Box 26)
- Poster -- Racism is Strictly Forbidden Here!!, 2011; cuid34927 (Box 27)
- Poster -- People Before Profit, 2011; cuid34889 (Box 28)
- Poster -- Arab Spring American Fall, 2011; cuid34890 (Box 28)
- Poster -- It is time to protect the people!, 2011; cuid34901 (Box 29)
- Poster -- OWS Thursday Schedule (9am to 9:30pm), 2011; cuid34902 (Box 29)
- Poster -- Street Medic Training, 2011; cuid34903 (Box 29)
- Poster -- Enjoy Your Capitalism, But We'll Never Let You Forget What It's Doing to Us, 2011; cuid34904 (Box 29)
- Poster -- Claw Back Wall $t Bonuses, 2011; cuid34930 (Box 30)
- Poster -- The World vs. The 1%, 2011; cuid34911 (Box 30)
- Poster -- Greed Kills, 2011; cuid34910 (Box 30)
- Poster -- "You Show Me a Capitalist and I'll Show You a Bloodsucker!" - Malcolm X, 2011; cuid34912 (Box 30)
- Poster -- I'm a Union Ironworker, I Vote, I Work, I Pay Taxes, I'm Pissed, So I'm Here. All the way from L.A., 2011; cuid34931 (Box 30)
- Poster -- Restructure mortgages. Keep Americans in their homes, 2011; cuid34878 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Poster -- Living Exercises, Stranger/Unstranger, 2011; cuid34888 (Box 33)
- Poster -- Trayvon Martin. Still, Still No Justice. Take it to the Streets. It's Up to Us!, 2011; cuid34886 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Poster -- Mic Check, 2011; cuid34917 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Posters, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 5-6, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Folder 1-6, Box 18, Folder 4-5, Box 19, Folder 3-13, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Folder 1-8, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Folder 1-10, Box 35, Box 36, Folder 8-9, Box 37, Box 39, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 7)